<resources>
    <string name="app_name">find doctor</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>

    <string-array name="header_string">
        <item>Flexi®</item>
        <item>Tylace™</item>
        <item>Virux®</item>
        <item>Virux® HC</item>
        <item>Benzapen ®</item>
        <item>Flexilax®</item>
        <item>Geston™</item>
        <item>Ketoral®</item>
        <item>Torax®</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="child_string">
        <item>Osteoarthritis, rheumatoid arthritis and ankylosing spondylitis</item>
        <item>As an adjunctive treatment for patients with abnormal,
        viscid or inspissated mucus secretion associated with conditions such as- Acute and chronic bronchopulmonary disorders
            (Pneumonia, Bronchitis, Laryngitis, Sinusitis, Tracheitis, Influenza, Emphysema, Tracheobronchitis, Chronic asthmatic bronchitis, Tuberculosis etc.), Atelectasis , Pulmonary complication of cystic fibrosis, Pulmonary complication of thoracic and cardiovascular surgery.
        </item>
        <item>Systemic Antifungal, Antiviral and Antiprotozoal Agents</item>
        <item>Skin Preparations</item>
        <item>Benzapen® injection is indicated in adults, adolescents, children and neonates for the treatment and prophylaxis of the following infections: For the treatment of:
- erysipelas
- syphilis: early syphilis (primary and secondary)
- latent syphilis (except for neurosyphilis and presence of pathological CSF findings)
- yaws
- pinta
For the prophylaxis of:
- rheumatic fever (chorea, rheumatic carditis)
- poststreptococcal glomerulonephritis
- erysipelas</item>

        <item>Flexilax® is indicated for the treatment of muscle spasm, muscle contraction,
            spasticity resulting from multiple sclerosis,
            spinal cord injuries and other spinal cord diseases,
            muscle spasm of cerebral origin especially infantile cerebral palsy,
            cerebrovascular accidents or neoplastic or degenerative brain disease, tension-type headache.</item>

        <item>Threatened Abortion, Habitual Abortion, Intrauterine Growth Retardation, Threatened premature delivery</item>

        <item>Treatment of superficial and deep mycoses : Infections of the skin, hair and nails by dermatophytes and/or yeasts (dermatomycosis, onychomycosis, perionyxis, pityriasisversicolor, chronic mucocutaneous candidiasis etc.) especially when topical treatment is difficult or not very effective,
            owing to involvement of large skin surfaces or to lesions affecting deeper dermal layers,
            nails and hairs ; Yeast infection of the mouth (oral thrush, perleche) and the gastrointestinal tract ; Vaginal candidiasis, especially chronic recurrent cases or cases responding poorly to topcial treatment ; Systemic mycotic infections such as systemic candidiasis, paracoccidioidomycosis,
            histoplasmosis, coccidioidomycosis etc.</item>

        <item>Short-term management of moderate to severe acute post-operative pain and acute pain of other origins.</item>


    </string-array>
</resources>